

PROFILE

My name is Hassan Mohamed. I am 34 years old. I am married. I have the experience and skills in a great way and have a distinct way of dealing with others and I try to understand everyone to bear the pressure of work and search for refueling significantly.

CONTACT

PHONE: 39628392 36577866

EMAIL:

bassrawe@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Reading Learning different things

Hassan Mohammed Ridha Abdulla Mohammed

EDUCATION

Guards Training School

2019

Basic Security Operative Refresher Course.

Guards Training School

2015

Basic Security Operative Course.

Excellence Training Solutions

2013

English

British Council

2012

English

Industrial Work Experience At E.K. Kanoo(Toyota)

2004

Auto Mechanics

WORK EXPERIENCE

G4S Secure solution - Security Guard

2015 - 2019

Tatweer Petroleum From July 2015 To Jan 2017 City Canter Mall From Jan 2017 To Sep 2018 Alba Line 6 Project From Sep 2018 To Jun 2019 City Canter Mall From Jun 2019 To 2019

Bahrain Workshop Company - Store Keeper

2012 - 2015

Ahmed Mansoor Al Aali - Salesman & Store Keeper

2006 - 2011

Hydraulic Mechanic From 2006 To 2008 Salesman & Store Keeper From 2008 To 2011

SKILLS

